{
 "1": {
   "question": "What's Principal Skinner's REAL name?",
   "answers": ["Robert Underdunk Terwilliger", "Armin Tamzarian", "Lyle Lanley"],
   "correct": 1
 },
 "2": {
   "question": "Who voices Homer's half brother, Herbert Powell?",
   "answers": ["Danny DeVito", "Phil Hartman", "Jon Lovitz"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "3": {
   "question": "What is Sideshow Bob's son's name?",
   "answers": ["Gianni", "Gino", "Giovanni"],
   "correct": 1
 },
 "4": {
   "question": "What is Homer Simpson's middle name?",
   "answers": ["Jerry", "JoJo", "Jay"],
   "correct": 2
 },
 "5": {
   "question": "Why does Homer end up in a mental institution, where he meets
   \"Michael Jackson\"?",
   "answers": ["He wears a pink shirt to work", "He does a poor job as Mr. Burns' assistant", "He choked the boy ONE too many times"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "6": {
   "question": "What's the name of the energy bar that Homer endorses?",
   "answers": ["Lightspeed Energy Bar", "Buzz Energy Bar", "PowerSauce"],
   "correct": 2
 },
 "7": {
   "question": "What common garden item is Sideshow Bob's arch nemesis?",
   "answers": ["Hoses", "Rakes", "Brooms"],
   "correct": 1
 },
 "8": {
   "question": "Who are the guest stars in the \"Lisa the Vegetarian\" episode?",
   "answers": ["Paul and Linda McCartney", "Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger", "Gillian Anderson and David Duchovny"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "9": {
   "question": "Who has had a creepy unrequited crush on Marge since high school?",
   "answers": ["Moe Syzslak", "Artie Ziff", "Seymour Skinner"],
   "correct": 1
 },
 "10": {
   "question": "What is Chief Wiggum's first name?",
   "answers": ["Clancy", "Carlton", "Clarent"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "11": {
   "question": "What is the name of Radioactive Man's sidekick?",
   "answers": ["Toxic Avenger", "Radioactive Boy", "Fallout Boy"],
   "correct": 2
 },
 "12": {
   "question": "What is the secret ingredient in a Flaming Moe?",
   "answers": ["Vodka", "Blueberry Syrup", "Cough Medicine"],
   "correct": 2
 },
 "13": {
   "question": "What is Marge's maiden name?",
   "answers": ["Onassis", "Bouvier", "Kennedy"],
   "correct": 1
 },
 "14": {
   "question": "What is the name of the company owned by Homer's former boss Hank Scorpio",
   "answers": ["Globex", "Scorpio Industries", "Compu-Global-Hyper-Net"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "15": {
   "question": "What game company released a Simpson's game around the same time as The Simpsons Movie?",
   "answers": ["Bethesda Softworks", "Blizzard-Activision", "Electronic Arts"],
   "correct": 2
 },
 "16": {
   "question": "What name does Homer have his legally changed to when a TV show steals his?",
   "answers": ["Max Power", "Guy Incognito", "Ned Flanders"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "17": {
   "question": "What drink is Homer disgusted by in the episode \"Homer vs New York\"?",
   "answers": ["Clam Juice", "Goat's milk", "Mountain Dew"],
   "correct": 2
 },
 "18": {
   "question": "What was the original color of Bart's shirt?",
   "answers": ["Blue", "Orange", "Red"],
   "correct": 0
 },
 "19": {
   "question": "They have ________ on computers now? - Homer Simpson",
   "answers": ["Games", "The Internet", "TV"],
   "correct": 1
 },
 "20": {
   "question": "Which friend does homer have to beat out so he can go on to be the first \"Average Joe\" in space?",
   "answers": ["Moe", "Barney", "Lenny"],
   "correct": 1
 }
}
